------------------OP-----------------------------
------------------ED-----------------------------
---------------------------------------------------------------------
誰か、そんな朝から
樱律联萌站 http://bbs.ylbud.com/
樱律联萌站为您带来高质量中日双语字幕
さぁ、新聞の勧誘にしてははずいぶん早いですね
中日双语字幕由 樱律字幕组 制作
Who'd visit this early in the morning?
感谢以下成员倾情制作
听译：五月、吉禾　校对：jez　时间轴：咲夜　后期：OMG
I couldn't say. It's quite early
for a newspaper salesman.
たのも
たのも？
魔王様、もしかして
Hail!
"Hail"?
Sire, could it be...
昨日の怪談の気味か
おそらく
たのも
- The one from the stairs yesterday?
- In all likelihood.
はい
朝早くに失礼する
Hail!
私は即日隣に引っ越してきたん鎌月鈴乃という
Y-Yes?
Forgive the early hour.
昨夜は出会いのは失礼をしたうえ
I am called Suzuno Kamazuki.
I moved next door yesterday.
お手数をかけたようで可笑しけない
I'm afraid not only did I commit
a rudeness before we met,
か、かたしけ？
ご丁寧にどうも
but I caused you trouble. I am most wretched.
Sadao
Maou
Shiro
Ashiya
改めてはじめまして
Wr-Wretched?
真央貞夫といいます
Uh, that's very courteous.
こっちらは引越しの挨拶と
お礼代わりにつまらないものだが
Pleased to formally meet you.
My name is Sadao Maou.
引越しの挨拶には
This is a small token of my thanks
and good wishes as your neighbor.
"Udon"
麺類が最適だと聴きを読んだ
これはわざわざどう
I'm told noodles are the
best gift for a new neighbor.
大丈夫ですか、魔王様
R-Right, that's very...kind!
何か
ええと
A-Are you all right, Sire?
失礼、私は芦屋と申しまして
- Wh-Why wouldn't I be?
- Er...
真央とは古い友人で
Ah, excuse me. My name is Ashiya,
and I'm an old friend of Maou's.
貴方がたの話はうかがっている
私はこちらの大家とは
あったことはないが
- I know of you two.
- A-Ashiya! H-Here, take this!
大家と思しき方からの手紙に
- I have never met the
landlady of this establishment,
- A-Ashiya! H-Here, take this!
困ったことがあれば
- I have never met the
landlady of this establishment,
- Oh, yes.
貴方がたに相談しろと書いてあった
- but I received a letter from
someone I believe to be the landlady
- H-Heavy!
その手紙に写真が同封されていた
instructing me to come
to you with any troubles.
I see...
There was a photograph enclosed...
いいや、いいや
それが大家に間違いありません
Yes, yes! That's certainly her.
とにかく
頼れる隣人というのは心強い
何どうぞ、長屋生活の至難をよろしく願いたい
In any case, I'm heartened
to have helpful neighbors.
長屋生活って
Would you be kind enough to
instruct me in tenement house living?
まだ何方か
最近増えた同郷人が一人
"Tenement house living"?
漆原です、よろしく
Is there someone else here?
引きこもりで～す
We gained another roommate recently.
好きで引きこもってんじゃないずの
I'm Urushihara! Hello neighbor!
なんでだろうが
"I'm a shut-in!"
それ、ちが
That ain't by choice!
Hmm, why is it?
なるほど、納得した
何をだよ
It's... that's... no...
では、今日はこれにで
I see. I get it.
今後どうも、よしなり
Get what?!
よ、よしなり
I'll excuse myself for now. Salutations,
and I hope we'll have a good relationship.
S-Salutations.
この瞬間
在这瞬间
この場所がスダート
这里就是起点
イメージして見よう
试着想象一下
Right here, this moment,
this is our starting point
何ができるのかな
我能做些什么
Let's picture what we might be able to do
信じられない出来事だってある
会发生些不可思议的事吧
もっと超えて行けるね
克服一切走的更远
Unbelievable things can happen sometimes
More... we can push past this
ゼロから生まれるすべて輝いて
从零重生的一切都特别耀眼
FLYあの空へ
翱翔朝着那片天空
Everything is born from zero;
I want to shine, flap my wings hard
思い切り羽ばたきたい
想尽情地展翅
最高のスマイルで笑いながら
以最完美的笑容
And fly to that sky
さぁ、行く
笑着前行吧
Come on, let's go, with
brilliant smiles on our faces!
未知の世界へと　今飛び出そうよ
奔向未知的世界仿佛就要飞出来
Let's fly off to an unknown world right now
未来を選び決めるのは自分
自己决定自己的未来
夢を追いかけて行　こう泣く日をある
追逐着梦想前进　也会有哭泣的日子
I decide, I'm the one who chooses my future
それは大事な願い消えないで
珍贵的愿望不会消失
Let's follow our dreams
Sure, some days we'll cry
It's a precious wish, don't disappear
きっと会えるから
一定可以再次遇
明日の君
朝着未来的你
I'm going after the future you,
because I know I'll find you
"The Devil is a Part-Timer!"
The Devil's Budget Is Saved by Neighborliness
魔王、近所付き合いで家計を助けられる
Hello!
- This is Emerada Etuva!
- I know that.
はい、こちら、エメイラドエドワイです
This is Yusa... I mean, Emilia.
I got a package that says it's
from you. What is this thing?
分かってるわよ
私、エミリアよ
Oh, so it arrived? That's amazing!
I only just sent it yesterday!
貴方の名前で荷物を届いているんだけど
何なのこれ
届きましたか
Talk about fast!
すごいですね
どうしたの、昨日なのに
It's celestial force!
Huh? Celestial force?
早いですね
I processed it into a form that wouldn't
seem out of the ordinary in Japan!
それは、聖法気です
聖法気？
日本で保存でも違和感もない形に
Eugh, "Holyvitan B"?
加工聖気式届きました
That's not a "b," it's a "β"!
Whatever, but basically you're saying
if I drink this, I can replenish my force?
ホーリービタンＢで
Ｂじゃなくで、ベイトです
"Holyvitan β"
That's right! But be very
careful about the dosage!
どうでもいいけど
つまり、飲めば聖法気を補充できるってこと？
Dosage? Is there a standard one or something?
でも、服用量は十分気を付けてください
Yep, please consider two bottles
a day to be the maximum!
服用量？メイアスとかあるの
はい、一日最大二本が限界と思ってください
You take one in the morning
and one in the afternoon,
but if you skip the morning dose,
you can't double up in the afternoon!
午前と午後に一本服用ですが
午前飲まなかったからって
Right... Okay, understood.
午後二本飲んだりしちゃだめですよ
Great! Please use it exactly
according to the instructions!
とりあえず、了解したわ
はい、用法用量守って正しくお使いください
Bye now!
Where is that girl, anyway?
Well, nothing ventured, nothing gained.
それじゃ
あの子、一体どこにいるの
物を試しよね
Why is the weather always so hot?
And those guys aren't up to much...
どうして毎日毎日こう熱いのよ
I feel like I'm sweating for nothing...
アイツらも特にこれで動きもないし
何か、汗かきぞ泣きかな
It's all about perspective!
It's good that they're just working and
eating like normal people, right? Peaceful!
ものが考えようよ
あの魔王一杯が毎日普通に
働いて食事しているだけなんで
平和でいいじゃない
But from some perspectives,
this makes me a stalker
lurking around a peaceful
all-male household, huh...
でも、考えようによっては
やっぱり平和に暮らしている男状態に
付き惑うストかこれ
Honestly! Can you not adequately
hang one piece of laundry?
You truly know nothing of
chores, do you, good Hanzo?
まったく、洗濯物質満足押せないのか
Ugh, lay off.
If you let clothes dry wrinkled,
they won't keep their shape.
本当に半蔵殿が家事をしらないのがな
- They will also dry unevenly.
- Hmm? Who's that?
うるさいな、もう
皺のまま干したら
Yeah, yeah, so sorry.
硬くずれするだろう
Jeez, you're seriously like a second Ashiya.
乾ずには塗らばれてる
誰
はいはい、すみませんね
- What?! What's going on?!
- You're tiresomely lazy.
もう、本当に芦屋がもう一人増えたみたいな
- Wait... is she a new demon?!
- If you're secluding yourself at home,
you ought to at least help with the housework!
何、どういうこと
Villa Rosa
Sasazuka
This is a little risky, but I've got no choice.
もしかして、あの女の子
新しい悪魔
You should get your act
together in times of crisis like this.
ちょっと危険だけど
仕方ないわね
Listen here. Chop the
Welsh onions, grate the ginger,
そんな時ぐらい半蔵殿きちんとしなくてどうする
and dilute the broth with cold water.
よろしいか
Now if you boil some udon,
you have a meal in a flash.
マンノ葱を刻んで生姜を磨りよろしいズイを冷水れれくしゃくする
Once they're done,
give them a quick rinse and you have
perfectly respectable cold udon.
これだけで後はうどんゆでれば
すぐに食事は整う
If we had a raw egg, it would be perfect.
茹でがあったら、冷水でさっと閉めれば
Ugh, you actually boil udon when it's this hot?
立派な冷やしうどん
生卵でもあれば完璧
The good Shiro does this
for three meals every day.
この熱いのに一々うどんゆでるの
Do you feel no filial piety?
四郎殿は毎日毎食これをしているのだ
Please keep at him, Miss Kamazuki.
少しは孝行しようとは思わないのか
He won't listen to these
things from his own family.
もっと言ってやってください、鎌月さん
Go on, grate some ginger.
Surely you can at least handle a grater.
誘致はいくら言っても聞きません
Roger...
ほら生姜をするよろせ
卸し金くらいは使えるだろう
Huh? Ashiya, are we out of ginger?
はい～よ
Ah, that's right, we used it up yesterday...
あれ、芦屋、生姜もうない
I beg your pardon, Miss Kamazuki,
but let's just add Welsh onions today.
そういえば、昨日使い切ったか
Urushihara!
- What are they even doing?
- No using the refrigerator to cool off!
すみませんが、鎌月さん
I shall go fetch some ginger from my room.
今日は葱だけで
漆原、冷蔵庫閉める
何やってんだか
Crap!
生姜なら、私の部屋に戻って取って来いよ
ヤバイ
Are you capable of using the stairs quietly?
M-Maou?!
Jeez, heroes shouldn't fall down the steps.
お前は静かに上りようにできるか
ま、魔王
たっく、勇者が階段でこうけんなよ
What are you two doing?
何してんだよ、二人ども
I apologize. This is because
I opened the door so suddenly.
No, it was nothing you did. It's my
fault for not watching my footing.
すまない
私が急に扉を開けたせいで
そんなじゃないの
Yep, totally. And she claims to be a hero...
私の不注意で
足元が下ろすになっただけだから
Yusa! I picked up most
of your stuff from outside.
まったくだ、これで勇者だったこれ
Oh, good work. Put it over there.
遊佐、外で散らばってた
ものに改め回収したけど
That high-and-mighty attitude pisses me off.
ご苦労様
And what even is this?
そこに置いといて
その超上から物にムカつくな
You drink health drinks?
Hey!
っていうか、何だよこれ
Drinking that stuff will give
you heat fatigue like Ashiya.
栄養ドリンクとか
ちょっと
What?! You've got heat fatigue?!
そんなの飲んでる芦屋みたいに夏ばてするよ
I fall ill sometimes,
just the same as anyone else.
あなた、夏ばてするの
It seems my gift was to blame.
私にたって具合が悪くなる時ぐらいある
I should have chosen something more nutritious.
原因は私のすわらしくでな
Oh, no, it's not your fault, Miss Kamazuki.
もっと栄養価の高い物
選ればよかった
Oh, I haven't introduced myself yet.
いや、鎌月さんのせいではありません
I moved in next door last week.
My name is Suzuno Kamazuki.
そういえば、申し遅れた
私は先週隣にばかりに引っ越してきた
As I come from an ancient and
old-fashioned family in a faraway land,
名を鎌月铃乃と申す
I'm still not well accustomed to Tokyo.
遥か土市の時代遅れの旧家出身ゆえ
I'd be most happy if
you'd instruct me in city life.
今だこの地の水に惨め切れずにいる
I guess we're about the same.
- Hmm?
- Oh, nothing!
都会生活の指導を賜れる幸いだ
I'm Emi Yusa. Nice to meet you.
同じくらいかな
Thanks for the food.
いや、遊佐恵美です、よろしく
Man, there's too much to do
and memorize. I'm so beat.
ご馳走さん
Your part-timing isn't anything new.
何かやることや覚えることが多すぎで
さすがに疲れるわ
While you've been lazing through life,
I've greatly matured as a human.
バードしているのは何時ものことでしょう
お前はぼさっと日々を過ごしている間に
In what way?
And you're not human.
俺は人間として一つ大きく成長しているんだぞ
Have you forgotten, Emi?
Just two days from now, on Sunday,
何をよ
っていうか誰が人間よ
I will become shift manager
at the Hatagaya MgRonald's!
忘れたか、恵美
明後日の日をから俺は
The deputy boss!
マクドナルド幡の谷売店の時間帯責任者
Uh-huh.
Hey! You don't believe me, do you?!
Shift managers get extra pay
and a position of responsibility!
店長代理人になるのだ
あっそ
信じてないだろう
What's hardest to believe is you
genuinely bragging about that to me.
時間帯責任者は手当ても付いて責任よるたじまなんだ
Well, fine. Eventually I'll claw my way
up to heights you can't even imagine!
あなたがそのことを真剣に
私に誇っているのは一番信じられない
まぁ、いい、いずれ俺はお前ら想像を付かない
- Are you an idiot?
- Hey, Yusa!
I cannot allow you to speak
to the head of our household...
高登り上ってつめてやる
阿呆じゃないの
- in that way...
- What?
こら、遊佐、我が家の主に対し
Good Emi, do you perchance have a
very close relationship with good Sadao?
その口の聞き方
許せるぞ
Huh?!
恵美殿はもしや貞夫殿と
That's not funny!
親密なお付き合いされているのか
Well... It's just that your
conversation flows so easily,
or rather, there seems to be
no restraint in your relationship...
冗談じゃないわよ
いや、二人の会話を聞いていると
気の置けないやりとりというか
Well, that's certainly one way to put it.
遠慮のない間柄だと見受けられるので
Don't you butt in!
We don't feel restraint, but more importantly,
まあ確かにものをいうだけのか
we don't feel trust, or friendship,
or anything positive at all!
余計なこというんじゃないわよ
遠慮はないけど
In fact, I pretty seriously want him
to drop dead, so let's get that clear.
それ以上に親友とか友情とか
プラスの感情は一切ないわ
むしろ、さっさと死ねばいいと
I-I see...
わりで本気で思っているから
I feel like I've seen this situation before...
そこだけは理解してよね
そ、そうか
何か、見たことある、この状況
I-I'm sure I'm reading this wrong,
but are you after Maou too?
まさかとは思うけど
Wh-What are you...?
あなたも真奥狙いなの
Wh-What if he overheard?!
な、何を
Huh? Oh... I'm sorry.
I really didn't think you were.
聞こえたらどうするつもりだろう
B-Be that as it may, I'm impressed.
ごめんなさい
What tipped you off?
本当にそうだとは思わなくて
I can't really explain it...
そ、それにしてもたいしたものだな
どうして分かった
どうしてって言われてもね
I'd better not say I've been through this before.
I just had a hunch, that's all!
前にも同じようなことあったなんで
I see. Impressive...
言わないほうがいいな
なんとなく、そう思っただけなんだけど
At first I thought she was an assassin
from Ente Isla, or a new demon,
そうか、さすがだな
最初は異世界からの視覚か
but it'd be odd for an assassin not
to make a move for a whole week,
あたまた新手の悪魔かと思ったけど
and for a demon, she's too polite to me.
近くなら引っ越して
一週間も何もしないのは変だし
Maybe I should give her a warning.
悪魔なら私に礼儀正しすぎる
Say, Suzuno. You might think this
is none of my business, but listen.
ここが言っておいた方がいいか
What is it?
ね、鈴乃ちゃん
You shouldn't get too close to him.
It'll only end badly for you.
ちょっと煩わしいと思うかもしれないけど
聞いて？
何だ
What do you mean?
アイツに近づくのは止めた方がいい
He's not the kind of man
a normal person can handle.
きっとあなたは不幸になるわ
それはどういう
It's best to steer clear if you can.
アイツは普通の人手におえるような男じゃないよ
B-But... I may not look it,
but I'm a seasoned warrior!
できれば近づかない方がいいわ
しかし、私はこう見えて、修羅場でくぐている
Still... Since this is coming
from you, I'll take care.
There must be something
about him that only you know.
だが　あなたがそういうのであればち調子よ
Nevertheless, it's too late for me to leave.
きっとあなたしか分からない何かがあるのだろう
I realize this is impertinent,
but would you lend me your aid?
そうはいっても
私はいまさらここを離れなれない
Sure, if I can.
ずうずうしいことは承知だが
You will? Then I can rest a little easier.
何とそ　助力願いたい
ええ　私にできることなら
I have an idea. Wait here a sec.
そうか
少しくれて安心できる
そうだ　ちょっと待ってて
You didn't get up to any funny
business while I was gone, did you?
I value my life more than that.
私がいない間にへんなことしなかったでしょうね
This is my cell number, email, and home address.
僕そんな命らずじゃないの
If these guys say anything awful
to you, ask for my help anytime.
これ　私の電話番語とメールアドレスと住所
Understood. I'm in your debt.
もしこいつらに何か言われたら
What do you think we are?
いつでも助け求めに来て
了解した　恩に着る
Bloodthirsty demons more
despicable than cockroaches.
お前　俺たちのこと何を思ってるんだよ
I'm sure I don't have to say this,
but FYI, if you pull anything with Suzuno
ゴキブリ以下の血飲んでたた魔物だと思ってるわ
I'll cut off your head and
display it on that windowsill.
いまさらないとは思うけど
Are you the evil sheriff now?
もし鈴乃ちゃんに変なことをしたら
そっくびはねて
Okay, I'm off.
そこの窓際に曝してあげるから
どこら悪官出るからお前は？
Don't worry, though. They're a more
law-abiding bunch than they look.
じゃ私はそろそろおいてますわ
See you later!
ま安心して
あいつらこう見えて
順法精神旺盛だから
それじゃね
I-I'm okay. I'm okay this time! Really...
大丈夫
今度は大丈夫だから　本当
She clear the K-point?
No, she saved herself from going all the way.
Seems like it.
界点越え？
Ow, ow, ow...
いや　途中で持ちこたえたぞ
みたいだね
いつつつ。。
じゃいってくるわ
Okay, I'm going.
May the tides of war be with you.
魔王様
ごぶんを
Don't worry about seeing me off, just stay in bed.
見送りはいいから
おとなしく寝てろ
Dealing with Emi totally saps my energy.
エミリ絡まれると
気力は一気に持って帰ろう
Good Sadao.
貞夫殿
Oh, Miss Kamazuki. Sorry about before.
ああ鎌月さん
先はどうも悪かったね
Did she say anything rude to you?
あいつ鎌月さんに失礼なこといわなかった？
No, nothing rude...
いや　そういうことはないが
All right, then.
ならいいけど
Well, I'm off to work.
じゃ俺これから仕事に行くんで
あのう　これ
Um, here. For you.
よかったら
Pardon?
はい？
So, how's the Holyvitan β working?
それでどうですか？
ホーリービタンＢの効き目は？
Well, I'm drinking it, but I haven't
had the chance to see any real effects.
ああ　飲んでることは飲んでるけど
これといた効果が見られる機会がなくてね
There haven't been any
battles or anything lately.
ここのところ戦うような時代もないし
Oh? So how are you getting on
with the Devil these days, then?
ああ　それじゃ最近と魔王とはどんな感じなんですか？
The same as ever. We basically
fight whenever we see each other,
今までと変わらないわ
顔合わせれば基本的にけんかするし
and we're both so busy with work
we don't have the energy for personal lives.
お互いに仕事が忙しくて
プライベートまでは気が回らなくて
You know, that's a typical complaint of
couples with not enough time together.
それって
仕事とが忙しくて
それ違いが多い恋人の口ですよ
Wh-Where did that come from, Eme?!
っば　な。。な。
何を言い出すのエメ
I'm Ente Isla's hero and he's the Devil!
私はエンテーイスラで勇者で合ってあいつは魔王よ
He's my enemy, whatever situation we're in!
どんな状況ならあいつは私の敵よ
C-C-C-Couple?! It makes me
furious just to think about it!
こ。。こ。。恋人とか考えなくて忌々しい
I was keeping tabs on him this morning,
and that's what I'm doing now!
今朝だって今だってあいつ見張っててね
- How can you suggest that when
you aren't even looking at us?!
- I know, I know.
見もしないで何いってんのよ
だってもさあ
Just please, Emilia, don't do anything
to set us against each other, okay?
でも　お願いですから
私とエミリアが敵対するようなことだけは
しないでくださいね
Don't worry, I'm a hero!
大丈夫
私は勇者よ
I swear on my mother's and father's
names that I won't make any mistakes.
父と母の名にかけて間違ったことはしないと誓うわ
So, how are things over there?
っで　最近そっちはどう
Well, none of the countries
have made any obvious moves.
そうですね
どこの国も
表だった動きはあまり見せてません
Any obvious moves.
表だった動きわね
Yes, that's right.
はい　そういうことです
I hear all sorts of information,
いろいろ情報は聞きますけど
but right now it's all just rumors.
うわさの行き打てませんからね
Also...
それと
Also?
それと何？
I heard that the Church's Missionary Division
協会の選挙部は
is trying to uncover the truth
behind Olba's disappearance.
オルバ行方不明の深層を探ろうとしているらしくて
It's possible that some may set
their sights on trying to find you, too.
もしかしたら
エミリアのことも探そうとしている人もいるかもしれません
Either way, please don't let your guard down.
いずれにしろ
油断はしないでくださいね
Some of them may be the
sort that would be willing to
中には好悪あせって
日本に迷惑をかける連中がいるかもしれませんから
cause trouble for Japan in order
to quickly achieve their goals, so...
I guess heroes can't ever catch a break, huh?
どんな状況でも勇者は一向楽できないわね
Seems like it.
そうですね
Well then... We'll rack up a big bill
if we're on the phone too long,
それじゃ
あんまりの海外が通話してると料金かさみますから
so I'm gonna hang up now.
そろそろお切りますね
Okay. Later, then.
うん　それじゃね
Sentucky
Fried
Chicken
As you know, tomorrow a restaurant that
is expected to pose a major threat to us,
知ってるとおり明日
つい我々の難敵となるであろう
Sentucky Fried Chicken,
will finally be open for business.
センターフライドチキンが新機開店する
I'll be out tomorrow afternoon, so I'll
be counting on you to run the ship, Maa.
まず私が不在となる
明日のごごの営業が
まく　君の総計にかかっているわけだ
Yes, Ma'am!
はい
Of course, in case there's an emergency,
もちろん緊急の場合想定し
I'll make arrangements so that
you can reach me at any time.
連絡は常時つくようにするが
But unless it's really serious,
go ahead and handle things on your own.
よほどの致命的な案件でない限りは
君の判断で事に当たれ
This is also for your personal growth.
これも君の成長のためでもある
Okay!
分かりました
There aren't many people working
tonight, so don't let your guard down.
今夜はシフトの末から
気を置くな
時間帯責任賞の仕事は始まってると思え
Consider your job as a shift
manager to have already begun.
What?
Shift Chart
At any rate, take a break now while you can.
とりあえず真奥君は
今のうちに休憩に入りな
18時までに戻ってくるなら
If you're gonna come back by
18:00, you can go have dinner.
ご飯食べてきてもいい
Or would you like to have some
free MgRonald's for dinner?
あそれとも
お店でマグナルドで食べるかい
I brought my dinner today, so...
あ今日　弁当持ってきてるんで
Oh, Mr. Maou, are you taking a break?
は　真奥さん　休憩ですか
Yeah, I thought I'd have dinner.
お　飯食おうかなって
Mr. Maou... is that...
真奥さん　それ
This? It's a lunch box.
これ？　弁当だけど
A lunch box? That's sort of
a simple but elegant lunch box.
お弁当？
なんか渋いお弁当箱ですね
Did Mr. Ashiya splurge on that?
アシアさんが奮発したんですか？
No, I'm borrowing it.
いや　借り物
To tell you the truth, a neighbor
recently moved in next door.
実はちょっと前に
隣の部屋に引越してきた人がいるさ
Next door? You mean
in that apartment house?
隣って　あのアパートに？
Yeah, it's a young lady.
若い女の子だけど
は？！女の子?!!
A-A lady?!
Don't suddenly start shouting like that!
いきなり大きな声出すんな
A-A lady?! You borrowed her lunch box?!
女の子って
その女の子弁当を借りたって一体どういうことですか？
What's this all about?!
千ちゃん　揺らすな揺らすな
Chi! Don't shake me! Don't shake me!
I-I-In other words, um... t-t-the lady
next door lent it t-t-to you, Mr. Maou?!
つまりその
隣の人が　ま　真奥さんに
Th-Th-That's right. Please stop shaking me!
そうそうだけど
お願いだから揺らすなよ
I'm sure... I'm sure it's not the case...
まさか　まさかと思いますけど
I'm sure it's not the case!
まさかと思いますけど
B-B-But is that homemade?!
手作りですか？
Y-Yeah, I-I think it's homemade.
多分手作りだと思うけど
- Ca-Ca-Ca-Ca-Ca...
- "Ca"?
みみみみみみ見せてもらっていいですか？
Ca-Can I see it?!
分かった　分かったからやめて
Okay! Okay! Just stop shaking me!
I'm begging you!
お願いだから
- New Year's dishes?
- "New Year's dishes"?
御節？
御節？
- Would you like to see
what's in the bottom box, too?
- W-W-W-Wait!
下の番も見る？
ま！待ってください！
I'm not mentally prepared yet!
まだ心の準備が
Uh, okay...
あ　はい
I can't shake this sense of dread!
Sheer adrenaline has brought me this far,
嫌な予感がしてたまらない
勢いここまで聞いてきただけど
but if this is my chance to turn back,
I probably should take it...
聞き返せならば
返したほうがいいんだけど
But... But... after coming this far,
there really is no turning back!
でも！でも！
ここまで来たならやっぱり返せない！
真奥さん　開けてください！
Mr. Maou! Please open the bottom box!
Y-Yes, Ma'am.
あはい！
"Friendly Market"
Welcome!
いらっしゃいませ
I spent another unexciting day stalking them...
今日も地味にストーカーしてしまったわ
I tend to buy the same stuff
every day without thinking, huh?
ついいつもの同じ買っちゃうんね
Thank you very much.
Please shop with us again.
ありがとうっざした
じゃくさくっしゃせ
Hm?! What just happened?!
うん　どんしたいまのは
Sir? Are you okay?
お客様大丈夫っすか？
危ない！
Stay back!
Stay inside! And call the police right away!
出てきちゃだめよ
それと　速く警察を
I don't know whether you're human or demon,
人間なのか　それとも悪魔なのか知らないけど
but why did you choose to attack me
in a conspicuous place like this?!
こんなに人目につく場所を沿ってくるなんて
どういうつもり？
私だけならともかく
It's one thing to come after me,
but if you're trying to cause trouble for
the people here, I'll show no mercy!
ここの人たちに迷惑をかけようというなら
許せはしないわ
What?! What happened?!
へ？なんなのこれ？
おい！
Take this!
逃げんな！
Stop!
あ　客様
Ah! Miss! Are you okay?!
大丈夫っすか？
Are you okay?
あなたこそ平気？
ごめんなさいね突き飛ばしちゃって
I'm sorry for pushing you away.
ああ大丈夫っす
Oh, I'm okay.
Really, I just hit my forehead, that's all.
っと　額根とがいたくらいたんで
Did you call the police?
警察に連絡は？
I think an emergency alert went to
the security company and the police.
ああ緊急通報で
警備会社と警察に連絡いってるはずなんて
- Oh, and, Miss...
- What is it?
ああで　お客様
何
I'm sorry, but the emergency manual states that
申し訳ないですけど
こういうときのマニュアルで
we're to have the customers remain
in the store until the police arrive.
店内の客様を
そのままにしておいてんっすよ
Could you wait until the police show up?
警察来るので
ちょっとここで待ってもらって　いいっすか
"Friendly Market"
It is working...
ちゃんと聞いてたわね
The Better Half that I activated this time...
今回発動させたベーターハーフ
It contained much stronger power than
the time I fought Lucifer two months ago.
二ヶ月前のルシフェルとの戦いのときより
ずっと強い力を内包していた
With this power, I might even be
able to use the Evil-Crushing Robe.
これなら
破邪の衣だって展開できるかも
But that just makes it harder to
figure out what that purple light was.
でも　それだけに
あの紫色の光の正体が分からない
I've never encountered an enemy who
nullified a sacred sword and celestial force.
聖剣や製法器を無効化するような敵には
であったこともないわ
Excuse me, Miss! These are yours, right?
あのう客様
これ　客様のですよね
ああごめんね
Oh, sorry. Thanks.
ありがとう
I-I like this music more than you'd think!
すきなのよ意外と
Oh, I see.
あそうっすか
Miss Yusa!
遊佐さん
Huh? Chiho?!
え　千穂ちゃん
Miss Yusa! There's trouble!
遊佐さん　大変です
Chiho, what on Earth happened?
千穂ちゃん　一体どうしたの？
真奥さんが　真奥さんが
Mr. Maou... Mr. Maou!
What happened to Maou?!
魔王が　どうしたの？！
Mr. Maou brought!
真奥さんが
真奥さんが持ってきたんです
Wh-What did he bring?
な　何を
A-A-A heart mark with a
lunch box that was in a homemade!
おおおお弁当つきハットマークの手作り
A two-layered lady! Two-layered!
女の子が二段かさみで
二段かさみで
Huh?
は？
一二三四
どこから朝になる
从何处开始是清晨
Where will morning start from, in this quiet sky?
静かな空
安静的天空
見ないふりをした指きり
装作没看见的拉钩
Fingertips twining in a pinky
swear I pretended not to see
恋日の先笑われた
恋爱之前被嘲笑
If the moon's been laughed at,
she'll sink away toward yesterday
つきなら  消えてゆくんだ
就算是月亮 也会要消失
昨日の方角
向着昨天的方向
うそつき　臆病者
胆小的人　说谎精
Liar, coward... if I'm all these things at once
みんなまとめて　  僕なら　最低言ったのは
大家总结的这些　　我的话   就说声差劲
Then I only blossomed in dreams
夢の中だ
在梦中
月の影に隠してた
藏在月影中
I hid in the moon's shadow,
but the truth is, I was crying
本当はね　泣いていだ
其实正在哭泣
The tears won't flow anymore...
did they all dry up?
涙はもう流れない
眼泪已经不再流
枯れてしまうたな
枯竭了吧
何もかも許せたら
虽然什么都原谅的话
If I could forgive everything,
maybe they'd flow again
流れるかもしれないけど
眼泪可能还是会流出来
But these are all things I want to protect
守りたいものばかりだなあ
全都是想要守护的东西
The Hero Enters the Fray